A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1977-1978
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files 1977-1978
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-2/1/2.801
This collection consists of 10,000 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1980 July 16.
Scope and Content Information
These files constitute the major record series generated by the president of the University of Virginia. The records consist chiefly of correspondence, but also include reports, minutes, clippings, memoranda, and related papers concerning all areas of business of the president's office.
The papers consist of general and administrative committee files.
Organization
SERIES I: General Records, 1977-1978, Boxes 1-22
SERIES II: Administrative Committees, 1977-1978, Boxes 22-23
SERIES III: Restricted Material, 1977-1978, Box 24
Contents List
- Series I: General Records
  - "A-Al" Miscellaneous--Gifts, Harry F. Byrd Jr., Albemarle County, Easters Weekend Parties near Biscuit Run 1977-1978 (Box 1)
  - "Am" Miscellaneous--Accreditation Notices, Grants, Awards, Fellowships 1977-1978 (Box 1)
  - "An-Az" Miscellaneous--Gifts; Jorge Luis Borges Collection; Evelyn Arnette vs University of Virginia, Discrimination Charge; Atlantic Richfield Foundation, The Henry Adams Project 1977-1978 (Box 1)
  - Admissions--General--Echols Scholars, Special Requests 1977-1978 (Box 1)
  - Admissions--Medical--Statistics 1977-1978 (Box 1)
  - Afro-American Affairs--Martin Luther King, Jr. Memorial Service; The dedication of the Luther Porter Jackson House 1977-1978 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Association--General--"The Vice President for Development," Duties and Responsibilities; Joe Palumbo, The Library Restaurant; Student Housing; Retirement of Clay Delauney 1977-1978 (Box 1)
  - Alumni-Bond Issue Response--Armistead L. Boothe 1977-1978 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Fund--Thank You Letters 1977-1978 (Box 1)
  - American Association of State Colleges and Universities--Office of Federal Programs 1977-1978 (Box 1)
  - American Association of University Professors--Surveys 1977-1978 (Box 1)
  - American Council on Education 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Annual Report--President's 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Anthropology 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions--Harry F. Byrd, Jr. 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Architecture--Accreditation of Landscape Architecture Degree Programs, Nomination of J. Norwood Bosserman for Fellowships in the American Institute of Architects, Possible Gift of Property in Vincenza from Mrs. Cabiana-Cita 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Army--JAG School--Naming the New Judge Advocate General's School Building 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Art 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Art--Bayly Museum--Establishment of the Bayly Museum Committee, Evelyn Bayly Tiffany Bequest, Gifts, Appraisal of K'ang Hsi Collection, Hugh Scott, Parking Lot Project 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Asian Studies 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Associated Western Universities 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Association of American Colleges 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Association of American Universities--Appropriations, Bakke Decision 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Association of American Universities--Basic Research Support from Industry, DNA Research, Health Manpower Legislation, Mandatory Retirement (3 folders) 1977-1978 (Box 3)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges 1977-1978 (Box 3)
  - Astronomy-- Mosaic(Volume 8, No. 6, Nov/Dec 1977) 1977-1978 (Box 3)
  - Athletics--General--Structural Failure at Scott Stadium, Scott Stadium being used for Charlottesville High School Night Games, Drowning in University Hall Swimming Pool, Pep Band's Parody of Maryland Ex-Governor Marvin Mandel, Parking and Transportation Program for Football Games, State Fire Marshal's Report on University Hall 1977-1978 (Box 3)
  - Athletics--ACC--Admission of Georgia Tech to ACC, Minutes 1977-1978 (Box 3)
  - Athletics--CFA 1977-1978 (Box 3)
  - Athletics--Finances 1977-1978 (Box 3)
  - Athletics--NCAA 1977-1978 (Box 3)
  - Athletics--Personnel 1977-1978 (Box 4)
  - Attorney General--State--License Agreements under Copyright Revision Act of 1976, Estate of Katie Eustace 1977-1978 (Box 4)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts 1977-1978 (Box 4)
  - "Ba-Bm" Miscellaneous--Gifts, Daguerreotype Portrait of Jefferson Davis, Office of International Student Advisor, Admissions Policy, Gifts to the Library, Children's Rehabilitation Center 1977-1978 (Box 4)
  - "Bn-Bz" Miscellaneous--Gifts; Gifts to the Library; Gifts to the Bayly Museum; Demolition of Brooks Hall; Harry F. Byrd, Jr. 1977-1978 (Box 4)
  - Biology 1977-1978 (Box 4)
  - Buildings and Grounds--Annual Report 1977-1978 (Box 4)
  - Business and Auxiliary Services--Water Conservation 1977-1978 (Box 4)
  - Business and Finance--Financial Report, 1976-1977 1977-1978 (Box 4)
  - "C-Chap" Miscellaneous--Gifts, Campbell vs Vining Litigation, Gay Student Union Office Space, Hubert H. Humphrey, Gifts to the Library, Warren Chapell 1977-1978 (Box 4)
  - "Char-Ck" Miscellaneous--Gifts, Service Charge for University Properties, City of Charlottesville and University Communications and Development 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - "Cl-Cz" Miscellaneous--Gifts, Gay Student Member Appointed as Co-Chairman of Student Resident Staff, The Henry Adams Project, McIntire Music Library, Permit Coordination Procedures for the Multiple Permit Process 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Career Planning and Placement 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Cavalier Daily--Public Access to Grade Distributions by Course and Instructor 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Chemistry--Grants, State Fire Marshal's Report on the Chemistry Building, Safety Needs 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Civil Rights 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Classics 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Clinch Valley College--Controversy with Paramount Minerals Corporation 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - College of Arts and Sciences 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - College Entrance Exam Board 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Commerce--Monroe Hill House Use 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Community Colleges 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Comptroller--State--Directives, "Preliminary Documentation for the Commonwealth Accounting and Reporting System" 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Comptroller--University 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Computing Activities--Proposed Move of Computing Activities to the State Farm Building, Procurement Procedures, Qualification Standards for Classifications, Salaries, Personnel Concerns, Quagliata Proposal, Minutes (2 folders) 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Congress 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Consortium--General--Continuing Higher Education 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Consortium--Central Virginia--UVA Offering a Master's Degree Program in Elementary Education in Fredericksburg 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Consortium--Northern Virginia--Salaries, "Virginia Employers View Vo-Ed Appendix," 1977 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Consortium--Tidewater 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Consortium--Valley 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Consortium--Western 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Continuing Education--UVA Library Science Extension Course 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Council of Presidents 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Council of Southern Universities 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - "Da-De" Miscellaneous--Gifts; John N. Dalton; HEW Guidelines on Affirmative Action; Harold Brown, Secretary of Defense 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - "Df-Dz" Miscellaneous--Gifts; DNA Research; The Henry Adams Project--Support from Walter G. Dunnington, Jr. and the Sprague Foundation; Grants; Jessie Ball DuPont Fund 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Danforth Foundation 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - Darden Graduate School of Business Administration--Undergraduate Library Plans, Admissions 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - Darden Graduate Business School Sponsors--"Frank L. Hereford, Jr./Ex-Officio/Trustee Workbook/1977-1978" 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - Dean's Meetings 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - Development--Jake Ewald's Tandem Research Project, Contacts with Parents, Funds 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - Drama--Heritage Repertory Theatre 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - "E" Miscellaneous--Gifts; Four Star Tennis Enterprise; Murrel Edmunds; Gifts to the Library; Estate of Katie Eustace; John A. Ewald, Jr.; Exxon Grants 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - Economics--Thomas Jefferson Center for Studies in Political Economy 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - Education--Leo Buscaglia Lecture; Purchase of State Farm Building; "A Proposal for a Family-Child Research Center for the University of Virginia," 1977; Grievance Action-Virgil S. Ward vs UVA; Proposal for New Unit, The Department of Education Research and Evaluation, UVA's Master Degree Program in Elementary Education 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - Energy--Federal--Federal Academic Science Funding 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - Energy--State 1977-1978 (Box 8)
  - Energy Research and Development 1977-1978 (Box 8)
  - Engineering and Applied Science--Electrical Service to Thornton Hall, Acquisition of State Farm Building, Interim Procedures for Reporting of Defects and Noncompliance (NCR), Abnormal Occurrences at the Reactor Facility, "A Preliminary Prospectus for Energy Policy Studies" by J.E. Gibson, Prospectus for a Three-Plus-Two Dual-Degree Program, Civil Wing Renovation (2 folders) 1977-1978 (Box 8)
  - Engineering and Buildings--State--State Fire Marshal's Reports on the Law/GSBA Dining Facility and the Radioactive Waste Management Facility, Acquisition of State Farm Building, Renovations to Aid the Handicapped 1977-1978 (Box 8)
  - Engineering--Research Labs for the Engineering Sciences (RLES) 1977-1978 (Box 8)
  - English--The Henry Adams Project 1977-1978 (Box 8)
  - Enrollment--General 1977-1978 (Box 8)
  - Environmental Sciences--Clark Hall's Electric System and Heating/Cooling System; "Virginia Climate Advisory," 1977-1978 issues; Aquatic Ecology Lab 1977-1978 (Box 8)
  - Equal Opportunity Programs--Evelyn Arnette vs UVA-Discrimination Charge 1977-1978 (Box 8)
  - "F" Miscellaneous--Gifts, McIntire Music Library, Heritage Theatre Group, Foreign Medical Schools 1977-1978 (Box 8)
  - Faculty--General 1977-1978 (Box 9)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences--Report on Women's Studies; Annual Report of the Dean of the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1977; New Registrar Selection 1977-1978 (Box 9)
  - Federal Executive Institute 1977-1978 (Box 9)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships--General 1977-1978 (Box 9)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships--DuPont Regional 1977-1978 (Box 9)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships--Love Foundation 1977-1978 (Box 9)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships--Rhodes 1977-1978 (Box 9)
  - Financial Aid to Students--Bulletin, 1976 1977-1978 (Box 9)
  - Fitzgerald Foundation 1977-1978 (Box 9)
  - Food Services 1977-1978 (Box 9)
  - Ford Foundation 1977-1978 (Box 9)
  - French Literature and General Linguistics 1977-1978 (Box 9)
  - "G-Gra" Miscellaneous--Gifts, Management Services for Former Vincent Estate, Camp Library, Memorial Proceedings for Judge Claude Vernon Spratley, Grants, Medical School Admissions 1977-1978 (Box 9)
  - "Gre-Gz" Miscellaneous--Gifts, Julian Green Collection, Grievance 1977-1978 (Box 9)
  - General Assembly--House Bill 30 and Amendments including 70/30 Plan, Bond Issue, Legislative Summaries, Medical Class Admissions (2 folders) 1977-1978 (Box 9)
  - General Assembly--House Appropriations Committee: "Amendments to House Bill 30," February 17, 1978; Remarks by Frank L. Hereford, Jr. to Committee 1977-1978 (Box 9)
  - German Language and Literature 1977-1978 (Box 9)
  - Gifts and Grants "A-D" 1977-1978 (Box 10)
  - Gifts and Grants "E-K" 1977-1978 (Box 10)
  - Gifts and Grants "L-R"1977-1978......Gifts and Grants "S-Z" 1977-1978 (Box 10)
  - Government and Foreign Affairs 1977-1978 (Box 10)
  - Governor's Office--Administration and Finance--Word Processing Equipment; State Climatologist-Interim Report; "Volunteerism in Virginia State Government," December 1977; Legislative Coordination and Clearance 1977-1978 (Box 10)
  - Governor's Office--Education:--Out-of-Country Travel Requests, Procurement of Computers, Affirmative Action, Issue Identification, Blue Ridge Sanatorium Transfer to UVA, Marine Science, Budget, Francis S. Quagliata's Proposal 1977-1978 (Box 10)
  - Governor's Office--General--Virginia Plan for Equal Opportunity, Board of Visitors Appointments, Medical School Admissions, Bond Issue 1977-1978 (Box 11)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences--Need for Fellowship Funds, High Baccalaureate Proposal 1977-1978 (Box 11)
  - Graphic Communications Office 1977-1978 (Box 11)
  - Graphic Communications--Printing Office 1977-1978 (Box 11)
  - Guggenheim Foundation 1977-1978 (Box 11)
  - "H" Miscellaneous--Gifts, Patent of Catheter Invented by John E. Hall, Texaco Support 1977-1978 (Box 11)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare--Affirmative Action, Handicapped Access, Student Financial Assistance 1977-1978 (Box 11)
  - Hereford, Frank L., Jr.--Personal 1977-1978 (Box 11)
  - Higher Education Act of 1965 1977-1978 (Box 11)
  - Higher Education Act--Title I 1977-1978 (Box 11)
  - Higher Education Act--Title III 1977-1978 (Box 11)
  - Higher Education Act--Title IV and V--Adams vs Califano 1977-1978 (Box 11)
  - Higher Education Act--Title IX 1977-1978 (Box 11)
  - Highway Department 1977-1978 (Box 11)
  - History--Virginia Governors Project 1977-1978 (Box 11)
  - Honor Committee and System 1977-1978 (Box 12)
  - Housing--Water Conservation, Problems/Complaints 1977-1978 (Box 12)
  - "I" Miscellaneous--Gifts; IBM Gift Program; ITT International Fellowship Program, 1976-1977; American Irish Foundation 1977-1978 (Box 12)
  - Institute of Government--Release and Assignment Agreement with The Michie Company re: Copyright 1977-1978 (Box 12)
  - Institutional Analysis 1977-1978 (Box 12)
  - Intergovernmental Affairs--State Planning--Indirect Cost Recovery, Legislation, Plans to Honor Weldon Cooper 1977-1978 (Box 12)
  - International Students--Investigation of Issues re: Lucy M. Hale, The International Student Advisor 1977-1978 (Box 12)
  - "J" Miscellaneous--Gifts, Luther P. Jackson House Dedication Ceremony and Speech, Repair of Thomas Jefferson Statue at Thomas Jefferson High School, Founder's Day, W. Alton Jones Foundation 1977-1978 (Box 12)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation--Gifts and Grants 1977-1978 (Box 12)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC) 1977-1978 (Box 12)
  - "K" Miscellaneous--Gifts, W.K. Kellogg Foundation, Edward M. Kennedy re: Foreign Medical Schools Legislation, Admission Policy, University Property on Oakhurst Circle 1977-1978 (Box 12)
  - "L" Miscellaneous--Gifts; CETA; Department of Labor Grants; Hearing Impaired Student Problems; Faculty Grievance Procedures; James F. Lewis, Jr. Gifts and the Establishment of Two Harry Flood Byrd, Jr. Professorships; Lloyd Lillie's Statue of Thomas Jefferson and the Seven Society, Mountain Lake Biological Research Station 1977-1978 (Box 12)
  - Law School--Center for Oceans Law and Policy--Doherty Lecture in Oceans Policy, Panama Canal Treaties Symposium 1977-1978 (Box 12)
  - Law School--General--John F. Merchant Award, Arboretum Committee, Compliant Alleging Discrimination in Faculty Hiring on the Basis of Race, Building and Maintenance Problems, Parking Problems 1977-1978 (Box 12)
  - Law School--General--North Grounds Parking and Housing Problems; Henry E. Howell, Jr.; Logistical Support; Biographical Data on Michael R. Hollis; "University of Virginia Law School Placement Office, Dean's Report, January 1, 1976-December 31, 1976" 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Law School--Report to the Office of Civil Rights (HEW)--Women Applicants for Administrative Positions 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Law Enforcement Education Program 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Legal Advisor--Cummings Estate "Overlook"; Lambeth Lane; Professional Liability of Employees who are Architects, Campbell vs Vining, Litigation 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Library--General--Gifts, Management Study, Records Management/Microfilming of Records 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - "M" Miscellaneous--Gifts, DuPont Company, Sears Building 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - "Ma-Me" Miscellaneous--Gifts; Personnel Matters; Josiah Macy, Jr. Foundation Faculty Scholars; Madison Bowl; Student Affairs; Dumas Malone; Mars Foundation; William C. Mott; Thurgood Marshall's Address at UVA's Graduation Ceremonies, May 21, 1978; Pep Band's Parody of Maryland Ex-Governor Marvin Mandel; Granville Meade Scholarships; Andrew W. Mellon Foundation 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - "Mi-Mon" Miscellaneous--Gifts; J. Harry Michael, Jr.-Legislation re: Blue Ridge Sanatorium and UVA Medical Center; Universities Involvement in South Africa, Gay Student Union 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - "Moo-My" Miscellaneous--Gifts, Claude Moore Health Sciences Library 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - McGregor Fund 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Madison House 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Marine Science 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Mariners Museum--Newport News (2 folders) 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Mary Washington College--Desegregation, Cooperation with UVA in Teaching Education Courses 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Mathematics 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Medical Center--Sources of Financing, Expansion of Office Space (1 of 3) 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Medical Center--Heliport, Emergency Medical Services, Gifts and Grants, Insurance and Legislative Concerns (2 of 3) 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Medical Center--Claude Moore Health Sciences Library Report, 1976-1977; Planning (3 of 3) 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Medical Center--Hospital--General--Free Service Memos, Volunteer Services 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Medical Center--Nursing--General 1977-1978 (Box 15)
  - Medical Center--Medical School--General--Gifts and Grants, Foreign Students 1977-1978 (Box 15)
  - Medical Center--Medical School--Advisory committee Meetings and Executive Committee Meetings--Minutes 1977-1978 (Box 15)
  - Medical Center--Medical School--Personnel 1977-1978 (Box 15)
  - Medical Center--Personnel 1977-1978 (Box 15)
  - Mental Health and Retardation 1977-1978 (Box 15)
  - Music--Presser Foundation Grant, Grant Requests 1977-1978 (Box 15)
  - "N-Ni" Miscellaneous--National Association Of College and University Business Officers, National Research Council, Harrison Nesbit, New Literary History1977-1978 (Box 15)
  - "No-Nz" Miscellaneous--Northern Virginia Community College, Nuclear Regulatory Commission 1977-1978 (Box 15)
  - NASA 1977-1978 (Box 15)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges (NASULGC)--Faculty Compensation, Collective Bargaining, Federal Aid, Budget Analysis FY79 (1 of 2) 1977-1978 (Box 15)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges (NASULGC)--Tax Appropriations, Minutes, Tuition (2 of 2) 1977-1978 (Box 15)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges--F.Y.I. 1977-1978 (Box 15)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities 1977-1978 (Box 16)
  - National Science Foundation--Reports and Proposals, Awards Procedure, Grant Policy Manual 1977-1978 (Box 16)
  - Naval Academy, U.S. 1977-1978 (Box 16)
  - Newcomb Hall 1977-1978 (Box 16)
  - "O" Miscellaneous--Oak Ridge Associated Universities; Olsson, S.G. 1977-1978 (Box 16)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa 1977-1978 (Box 16)
  - "P" Miscellaneous--Gay Student Union; Patent Policy; Pearman, Stuart; Poe Room 1977-1978 (Box 16)
  - Parking and Transportation Services 1977-1978 (Box 16)
  - Personnel--Employee Relations 1977-1978 (Box 16)
  - Personnel--General--Student Worker Pay Rates, EEO 1977-1978 (Box 16)
  - Personnel and Training--EEO 1977-1978 (Box 16)
  - Physical Planning--TDX (Telephone System), Parking and Bus Philosophy, Asbestos 1977-1978 (Box 16)
  - Physics 1977-1978 (Box 16)
  - Planning--Project Status Reports 1977-1978 (Box 16)
  - Planning and Budget--State--Budget Manual, Population Projections 1977-1978 (Box 16)
  - Planning and Budget--Capital Outlay 1977-1978 (Box 17)
  - Planning and Budget--Medical--Capital Outlay 1977-1978 (Box 17)
  - Planning and Budget--UVA--Budget Manual 1977-1978 (Box 17)
  - Promotions 1977-1978 (Box 17)
  - Property Records and Insurance 1977-1978 (Box 17)
  - Provost for the University--Affirmative Action, Faculty Appointments and Elections 1977-1978 (Box 17)
  - Associate Provost for Research--Funding and Appropriations 1977-1978 (Box 17)
  - Psychology 1977-1978 (Box 17)
  - Purchase and Supply 1977-1978 (Box 17)
  - Purchasing 1977-1978 (Box 17)
  - "Q" Miscellaneous 1977-1978 (Box 17)
  - "R-Re" Miscellaneous--Tuition Tax Credits, Virginia Domiciliary Status, Gifts, Rehabilitation Engineering Center Annual Report, Research Corporation 1977-1978 (Box 17)
  - "Rh-Rz" Miscellaneous--Gifts; Robb, Charles S.; J. Kenneth Robinson; Rockefeller Foundation 1977-1978 (Box 17)
  - Recommendations (Restricted) 1977-1978 (Box 17)
  - Registrar--Position Reclassification 1977-1978 (Box 17)
  - Religious Studies 1977-1978 (Box 17)
  - ROTC--General--Joint Military Activities 1977-1978 (Box 17)
  - ROTC--Air Force 1977-1978 (Box 17)
  - ROTC--Army 1977-1978 (Box 17)
  - ROTC--Navy 1977-1978 (Box 17)
  - "Sa-Sl" Miscellaneous--Gifts; Satterfield, D.E.; Schlesinger, James; Rotunda Clock; William L. Scott; SESAC, Inc. 1977-1978 (Box 18)
  - "Sm-Ss" Miscellaneous--Gifts, Handicapped Access, Pipe Organs, Society of the Cincinnati, Society of the Purple Shadows, South Africa/Sullivan Principles, So. Regional Education Board 1977-1978 (Box 18)
  - "St-Sz" Miscellaneous--Gifts, Undergraduate Admissions Policy, National Education Training Program 1977-1978 (Box 18)
  - Safety and Security 1977-1978 (Box 18)
  - Senate--University--Roster, Minutes 1977-1978 (Box 18)
  - Slavic Languages and Literature 1977-1978 (Box 18)
  - Sociology 1977-1978 (Box 18)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools--Institutional Profile (UVA) 1977-1978 (Box 18)
  - Southern Association of Land-Grant College and State Universities 1977-1978 (Box 18)
  - Southern Fellowships Fund 1977-1978 (Box 18)
  - Southern Regional Education Board--Academic Common Market 1977-1978 (Box 18)
  - Space and Energy Management 1977-1978 (Box 18)
  - Spanish, Italian, and Portuguese--Minorities 1977-1978 (Box 18)
  - Speeches--Finals, Alumni Awards, Founder's Day, University Union, Thomas Jefferson Society, Norfolk Rotary Club, "Our Man in Wilmington," Panama Canal Treaties Symposium, Appropriations Committee/House of Delegates Hearings, Med. Alum. Advisory Committee and Board, Fall Convocation, Lawn Society, Introduction to Governor Godwin, New Faculty, Graves Mountain, Entering Students, Resident Staff 1977-1978 (Box 19)
  - Sponsored Programs--Proposals and Awards 1977-1978 (Box 19)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV)--Planning, Graduate Marine Science (1 of 4) 1977-1978 (Box 19)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV)--Policies and Procedures, Appropriations, Minutes (2 of 4) 1977-1978 (Box 19)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV)--Capital Outlay, Policies and Procedures, Scholarships, Marine Science, Regional Computing Centers (3 of 4) 1977-1978 (Box 19)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV)--Paso Speech, Cost Study Data, Degree Productivity Study (4 of 4) 1977-1978 (Box 19)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV)--Council Notes 1977-1978 (Box 19)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV)--Mission Explication Committee--Tidewater Study, Institutional Summary Statements for Ad Hoc Committee on Development of Institutional Profiles 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - State Department of Education 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - State Farm--Purchase and Lease, Use 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - State Fire Marshal--Medical Center Sprinkler System, Inspections 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - State, U.S. Department of 1977-1978 (Box 20)